As a brand, the relationship you have
with your customers is built on trust.
When a customer buys one of your products,
they expect the item to be authentic,
and most likely it is.
However, customers' trust can be broken
if they receive a counterfeit product.
Transparency is a product serialization service
that can help you protect your brand
and keep your customers' trust
by identifying individual units
and preventing counterfeits from reaching customers.
Here's how it works.
You tell us which products you want to enroll,
then share your product information.
We will use that information to generate transparency codes
with our secure software.
Each code is unique and should be added
to every unit you manufacture.
When transparency checks are turned on,
anyone selling your enrolled products in Amazon stores
will need to provide valid transparency codes
before they add their offer to your listing
or create one of their own.
We'll also verify transparency codes
before the order is shipped,
regardless of whether it's fulfilled by Amazon
or a third-party seller.
If the right code isn't there, it won't ship.
Ensuring customers only receive genuine items.
Transparency code required customers
can also confirm authenticity of your products
no matter where they are purchased
with the Amazon Shopping app or the Transparency app.
You can even share product information,
videos, images and promotions.
Ready to get started with transparency?
Find a step-by-step walkthrough of the onboarding process
by searching Transparency onboarding guide
in Seller University.